KUNYI LU

Apt 2B, 2421 Lancashire Dr, Ann Arbor, MI, 48105 734-7737646 \(\rightarrow \text{lukunvi@umich.edu} \(\rightarrow \text{www.linkedin.com/in/kunvilu} \)

SUMMARY

A second year Master student with 4 years experience in machine learning and computer vision

Proficient in Python and computer vision/machine learning toolkit, such as OpenCV, TensorFlow, PyTorch and so on Interested in computer vision, natural language processing and machine learning

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Electrical & Computer Engineering

September 2017 - May 2019

University of Michigan, Major: Machine Learning, GPA: 3.92/4.0

Related Courses: Computer Vision(A+), Natural Language Processing(A+)

Bachelor of Science in Electronic & Computer Engineering

September 2013 - June 2017

Wuhan University, GPA: 3.83/4.0, Ranking: top 5%

Related Courses: Programming fundamentals, Object-Oriented Programming, Computer Networks

WORK EXPERIENCE

Video Understanding for City Security

February 2018 - August 2018 Voxel51, LLC, Ann Arbor, MI

Computer Vision Software Engineer Intern

- Implemented a powerful system for tracking multiple objects using machine learning models that achieves a high accuracy above 90% in average
- Generated a dataset for pedestrian action recognition and trained micro-action classifiers (machine learning models) on the dataset
- · Developed a FashionSense pipeline that can detect and track fashion clothes/accessories in movies
- · Developed a PersonSense pipeline that can detect, track pedestrians and recognize their action
- · Collaboratively developed a VehicleSense pipeline that can detect, track vehicles and recognize their color, make and model

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Temporally-Aware Interpolation Network for Video Frame Inpainting

September 2018 - Current

Research Assistant

Vision and Robotics Lab. University of Michigan

Advisor: Jason J. Corso

- · Implementing a novel deep network for video frame inpainting which generates more accurate and visually pleasing predictions than multiple strong baselines
- Designed multiple experiments to demonstrate our model's ability to perform well on complex videos depicting challenging scenes and a wide variety of actions

Local Feature Matching

December 2016 - June 2017

Research Assistant Advisor: Jiayi Ma

Multi Spectral Vision Processing Lab, Wuhan University

- Proposed an efficient algorithm for establishing robust point correspondences between two sets of points
- Improved feature matching accuracy compared with SIFT by reducing outliers

HandWritten Character Recognition on Express Sheet Information

Research Assistant & National Project Team Leader

May 2015 - September 2016

DSP Lab, Wuhan University

Advisor: Dexiang Deng

- · Led a 5-members team to develop an Android APP that can identify the handwritten phone number on express sheet and notify the receiver to take delivery by sending message automatically
- · Took responsibility to implement and improve handwritten character recognition by using CNN+SVM trained on MNIST

PUBLICATIONS AND PATENTS

[1] Ryan Szeto, Ximeng Sun, Kunyi Lu, Jason J.Corso, "A Temporally-Aware Interpolation Network for Video Frame Inpainting", IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON PATTERN ANALYSIS AND MACHINE INTELLIGENCE (submitted)

[2] Kunyi Lu, Yuting Chen, Xinjue Hu, Xiaoqiao Chen, "An Express Scanner", Chinese Patent for utility model, Nr. ZL 2016 2 0302472.7

[3] Yuting Chen, Kunyi Lu, Yanyu Qu, Xiaoqiao Chen, "An Intelligent Express Box with Multi-functional Scanner", Chinese Patent for utility model, Nr. ZL 2016 2 0297570.6

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Development Language: Python, C/C++, Julia, Shell Scripting, Matlab, HTML, JavaScript

Operating Systems: Linux/Unix, Windows

Computer Vision Tools: OpenCV, TensorFlow, PyTorch, CUDA